suitesmart.com 2004-04-11

# SuiteSmart: Company: Privacy

**SuiteSmart Privacy Policy**

SuiteSmart is committed to protecting your trust and privacy. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information such as your name, address or email is automatically collected when visiting this website. We do not use cookies on our website. 

Participation in Online Surveys

SuiteSmart conducts online surveys to understand the attitudes and opinions of consumers as a whole. Your responses are grouped with the responses of others to form summary information that companies can use to understand the needs and perceptions of consumers and improve the products and services they offer. 

In these surveys, we may ask you many different kinds of questions about your attitudes and opinions towards certain products and services. This information is only used in aggregate form, and is never traced back to you personally. 

Protecting Your Privacy

The following rules underscore SuiteSmart's commitment to your trust and privacy: 

  * We do not sell anyone's name or other information to a mailing list or any other outside marketing companies. 
  * We only collect individually identifiable information only in order to contact prize-winners in a sweepstakes, or if a person has explicitly indicated that we may re-contact them for other purposes, such as to take part in a follow-up survey or to join an online research panel. We will never sell, share or otherwise distribute this information to third parties. For all other purposes, only aggregate data is used, or data which has been stripped of all personally identifiable or sensitive data. 
  * We take all reasonable steps to protect the security and integrity of the information that respondents provide. 
  * Respondents have the right to check the data that has been collected and to correct inaccurate personal information. 
  * Children aged 13 and under are not eligible for SuiteSmart surveys. If any data is determined to have been provided by children aged 13 and under, that data is removed from the database. 

Types of Information Collected

SuiteSmart primarily collects consumer opinions about specific products and services. In addition, we sometimes collect behavioral data, such as how many times an advertisement was seen. We gather behavioral data through the use of cookies. See below for more information about SuiteSmart's use of cookies. In some cases we do collect personally identifiable information such as email address in order to contact you if you have won a prize. 

Use of Collected Information

The data we collect is used only in aggregate form to gain an understanding of the attitudes of the surveyed population as a whole. We do not connect responses directly to an individual. Personally identifiable information is used only to contact you if you are a prize winner, or if you have explicitly asked us to participate in a research panel. We never sell, share, or distribute this information with any third parties. 

Use of Cookies

Interactive research often requires us to associate short pieces of text, commonly referred to as "cookies," with users' web browsers. A cookie allows us to recognize a web browser, but does not give any personal identifying information about the user. We primarily use cookies to avoid inviting someone using that web browser to take the same survey twice. 

If cookies are turned off, we are unable to recognize whether or not someone has been offered a survey, and may inadvertently offer them the same survey in the future. 

More Information 

For more information about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@suitesmart.com](mailto:privacy@suitesmart.com), or send mail to: 

**SuiteSmart, Inc**  
Consumer Privacy Dept.  
1005 Market Street  
San Francisco, CA 94013   

|  |
